Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records UA037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty meeting minutes, 1854 -- 2019; UA037.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 55 Volumes; 431 Digital Object(s); 938 Megabytes 429 of 431 digital objects comprise 938 megabytes.
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2018 -- 2019; UA037.001300; 37.6 Megabytes; 49 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 May 16; UA037.001348; 89.7 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curricula agenda, 2019 May 16; UA037.001349; 541.5 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, Fall 2019; UA037.001350; 2.9 Megabytes; 15 Digital Object(s)
    - Department chairs minutes, 2019 September 18; UA037.001351; 245.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2019 September 25; UA037.001352; 260.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 September 25; UA037.001353; 254.8 Kilobytes
    - Complete text of the by-laws of the Faculty of the School of Arts and Sciences, 2019 September 25; UA037.001354; 204.3 Kilobytes
    - Curricula agenda, finalized, 2019 September 25; UA037.001355; 241.3 Kilobytes
    - Departments chairs meeting minutes, final, 2019 October 23; UA037.001356; 272.1 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda two, 2019 October 30; UA037.001357; 77.3 Kilobytes
    - School of the Museum of Fine Arts course changes, 2019 October 30; UA037.001358; 54.9 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2019 November 13; UA037.001359; 93.2 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 November 13; UA037.001360; 55.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting, 2019 November 20; UA037.001361; 442.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2019 November 20; UA037.001362; 260.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 November 20; UA037.001363; 290.3 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curricula agenda, 2019 November 20; UA037.001364; 105.8 Kilobytes
    - Departments chairs meeting minutes, 2019 December 11; UA037.001365; 233.8 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2014 -- 2015; UA037.001366; 7.2 Megabytes; 25 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2014 August 27; UA037.001367; 397 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting script, 2014 August 27; UA037.001368; 90.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering reorganization proposal, 2014 September 03; UA037.001369; 126.2 Kilobytes
    - Provosts meeting agenda and briefing, 2014 September 03; UA037.001370; 28.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2014 September 14; UA037.001371; 180.1 Kilobytes
    - Childcare faculty open letter to administration, 2014 September 17; UA037.001372; 121.5 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee online teaching evaluations proposal, 2014 September 17; UA037.001373; 47.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2014 October 08; UA037.001374; 298 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee online teaching evaluations proposal, 2014 October 08; UA037.001375; 47.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2014 November 12; UA037.001376; 413.2 Kilobytes
    - Indigenous Peoples Day resolution, passed, 2014 November 12; UA037.001377; 109.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2014 December 03; UA037.001378; 410 Kilobytes
    - Committee Reports on Arts, Sciences, and Engineering reorganization proposal, 2014 December 03; UA037.001379; 764.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2015 February 04; UA037.001380; 96.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 February 04; UA037.001381; 996.5 Kilobytes
    - International travel policy Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting presentation, 2015 February 04; UA037.001382; 578.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 February 25; UA037.001383; 995.2 Kilobytes
    - Statement 11 on tenure and promotion process, 2015 February 25; UA037.001384; 136.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 March 25; UA037.001385; 854 Kilobytes
    - Indigenous Peoples Day resolution and justification, 2015 March 25; UA037.001386; 230.2 Kilobytes
    - Interdisciplinary tenure and promotion proposal, February 2015, 2015 March 25; UA037.001387; 38.4 Kilobytes
    - Interdisciplinary tenure and promotion proposal, March 2015, 2015 March 25; UA037.001388; 38.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 April 29; UA037.001389; 153.6 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal assigning credit to courses, 2015 April 29; UA037.001390; 53 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 May 13; UA037.001391; 356.9 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2015 -- 2016; UA037.001392; 8.7 Megabytes; 25 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 September 02; UA037.001393; 661.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 September 30; UA037.001394; 264.4 Kilobytes
    - Concussion letter to faculty, 2015 September 30; UA037.001395; 63.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 October 28; UA037.001396; 461.2 Kilobytes
    - Diversity Fund September Summary, 2015 October 28; UA037.001397; 14.9 Kilobytes
    - Diversity Inclusion and Disability presentation, 2015 October 28; UA037.001398; 797.7 Kilobytes
    - Proposed Bylaw Change to Tenure and Promotion, 2015 October 28; UA037.001399; 18.2 Kilobytes
    - Summary of Changes to Handbook 2015, 2015 October 28; UA037.001400; 19.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2015 December 02; UA037.001401; 553.6 Kilobytes
    - Diversity, inclusion, and disability presentation, 2015 December 02; UA037.001402; 797.7 Kilobytes
    - Divestment frequently asked questions, 2015 December 02; UA037.001403; 222.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 February 03; UA037.001404; 133.1 Kilobytes
    - Learning spaces assessment study executive summary, 2016 February 03; UA037.001405; 190.9 Kilobytes
    - Summary of changes in Statement 11 for 2016, 2016 February 03; UA037.001406; 17.2 Kilobytes
    - Dependent care survey executive summary, 2016 February 24; UA037.001407; 716.1 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee evaluation and grades proposal, 2016 February 24; UA037.001408; 31.6 Kilobytes
    - Resolution calling for Tufts University to recognize the historical and present day significance of celebrating Indigenous Peoples Day in place of "Columbus Day", 2016 February 24; UA037.001409; 36.1 Kilobytes
    - Amended and approved Educational Policy Committee proposal course evaluation results, 2016 March 30; UA037.001410; 27.8 Kilobytes
    - Amended and approved Educational Policy Committee proposal on incomplete grades, 2016 March 30; UA037.001411; 13.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 March 30; UA037.001412; 10.1 Kilobytes
    - Faculty advisory board executive committee by-law revision proposal, version 3, 2016 March 30; UA037.001413; 23.9 Kilobytes
    - Residential strategies working group PowerPoint, 2016 March 30; UA037.001414; 2.5 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 May 04; UA037.001415; 252 Kilobytes
    - Dependent care presentation, 2016 May 04; UA037.001416; 659.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 May 18; UA037.001417; 353 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2016 -- 2017; UA037.001418; 39.0 Megabytes; 36 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 August 31; UA037.001419; 274.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 September 21; UA037.001420; 107.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2016 September 21; UA037.001421; 87.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2016 October 19; UA037.001422; 89.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 October 19; UA037.001423; 208.8 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal on campus closure make up policy, 2016 October 19; UA037.001424; 41 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2016 November 16; UA037.001425; 96 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 November 16; UA037.001426; 113.6 Kilobytes
    - Defining the ombudsperson role at Tufts, 2016 November 16; UA037.001427; 50.5 Kilobytes
    - Proposal to have only full professors deliberate on promotion cases, 2016 November 16; UA037.001428; 14.4 Kilobytes
    - Tenure and promotion slides for faculty meeting, 2016 November 16; UA037.001429; 93.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2016 December 14; UA037.001430; 97.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 December 14; UA037.001431; 118.1 Kilobytes
    - Defining the ombudsperson role at Tufts, 2016 December 14; UA037.001432; 50.5 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee make up day proposal, revised, 2016 December 14; UA037.001433; 41.7 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal regarding changes to Bulletin, 2016 December 14; UA037.001434; 166.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2016 December 24; UA037.001435; 287 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2017 February 08; UA037.001436; 89.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 February 08; UA037.001437; 220.2 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee Bulletin language for academic year 2018 -- 2019, 2017 February 08; UA037.001438; 166.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering capital plan projects update, 2017 March 01; UA037.001439; 21.7 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 March 01; UA037.001440; 74.8 Kilobytes
    - Student Life Review Committee: engagement opportunities and update on capital planning and projects, 2017 March 01; UA037.001441; 119.7 Kilobytes
    - Proposed by-law changes from the faculty research support and Facilities Advisory Committee, 2017 March 01; UA037.001442; 18.8 Kilobytes
    - Proposed calendars for 2020 -- 2025, 2017 March 01; UA037.001443; 168.2 Kilobytes
    - Two-factor authentication awareness presentation, 2017 March 29; UA037.001444; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2017 March 29; UA037.001445; 85.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 March 29; UA037.001446; 322.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty summer at Tufts, 2017 March 29; UA037.001447; 1 Megabytes
    - Revised academic calendar, 2020 -- 2025, 2017 March 29; UA037.001448; 173 Kilobytes
    - Tufts travel insurance presentation, 2017 March 29; UA037.001449; 1.6 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2017 April 26; UA037.001450; 81.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 April 26; UA037.001451; 360.5 Kilobytes
    - Dependent care update, 2017 April 26; UA037.001452; 151.6 Kilobytes
    - Strategic research and scholarship Arts, Sciences, and Engineering meeting, 2017 April 26; UA037.001453; 11.5 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 May 17; UA037.001454; 298.8 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2017 -- 2018; UA037.001455; 69.1 Megabytes; 39 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2017 August 29; UA037.001456; 80.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 August 29; UA037.001457; 711.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering summer at Tufts, 2017 September 13; UA037.001458; 296.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 September 13; UA037.001459; 133.4 Kilobytes
    - Credit conversion update, Fall 2017, 2017 September 13; UA037.001460; 379.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2017 October 18; UA037.001461; 84.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 October 18; UA037.001462; 243.4 Kilobytes
    - Student life review committee presentation, 2017 October 18; UA037.001463; 9.5 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2017 November 08; UA037.001464; 84.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 November 08; UA037.001465; 353.6 Kilobytes
    - Brighter World Campaign update presentation, 2017 November 08; UA037.001466; 11.6 Megabytes
    - November Board of Trustees report, 2017 November 08; UA037.001467; 9.6 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2017 December 13; UA037.001468; 478.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2017 December 13; UA037.001469; 422.9 Kilobytes
    - Budget and priorities proposed by-law change, 2017 December 13; UA037.001470; 86.8 Kilobytes
    - Facilities update, 2017 December 13; UA037.001471; 2 Megabytes
    - Federal issues update, 2017 December 13; UA037.001472; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 February 07; UA037.001473; 237.6 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposals, 2018 February 07; UA037.001474; 56.8 Kilobytes
    - Pass-fail deadline, Tufts Community Union resolution, 2018 February 07; UA037.001475; 418.1 Kilobytes
    - Tisch College update, 2018 February 07; UA037.001476; 23 MB Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 February 28; UA037.001477; 87.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 February 28; UA037.001478; 225.3 Kilobytes
    - Board of Trustees report, 2018 February 28; UA037.001479; 3.2 MB Megabytes
    - Letter to the Tufts University administration and Board of Trustees, 2018 February 28; UA037.001480; 33.5 Kilobytes
    - Mental Health Task Force background for Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting, 2018 February 28; UA037.001481; 492.1 Kilobytes
    - Mental Health Task Force update, Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting, version 3, 2018 February 28; UA037.001482; 2.2 MB Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering meeting agenda and briefing updated, 2018 March 28; UA037.001483; 218 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 March 28; UA037.001484; 176.9 Kilobytes
    - Biomedical engineering co-op supporting documents, 2018 March 28; UA037.001485; 1.6 MB Megabytes
    - Update on data intensive studies at Tufts, 2018 March 28; UA037.001486; 1.8 MB Megabytes
    - Divestment letter to the Tufts University administration and Board of Trustees, 2018 March 28; UA037.001487; 33.5 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee block schedule proposals, 2018 March 28; UA037.001488; 39.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 April 25; UA037.001489; 223 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 April 25; UA037.001490; 168.6 Kilobytes
    - Recommendations for the management and development of Tufts faculty housing resources, 2018 April 25; UA037.001491; 388.3 Kilobytes
    - Tenure and promotion slides on outside experts, 2018 April 25; UA037.001492; 365.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2018 May 16; UA037.001493; 216.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 May 16; UA037.001494; 107.4 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2018 -- 2019; UA037.001495; 15.6 Megabytes; 33 Digital Object(s)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 2018 August 28; UA037.001496; 186.2 Kilobytes
    - New faculty bios, 2018 August 28; UA037.001497; 166.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 September 12; UA037.001498; 220.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 September 12; UA037.001499; 177.4 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee drop date proposal, 2018 September 12; UA037.001500; 38.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 October 17; UA037.001501; 121.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 October 17; UA037.001502; 227.5 Kilobytes
    - Code of conduct updates, Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty presentation, 2018 October 17; UA037.001503; 5.9 MB Megabytes
    - Revised grievance panel procedures and by-laws, 2018 October 17; UA037.001504; 139.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 November 07; UA037.001505; 122.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 November 07; UA037.001506; 211.1 Kilobytes
    - Student by-law proposals, 2018 November 07; UA037.001507; 319.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2018 December 12; UA037.001508; 121.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2018 December 12; UA037.001509; 86.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering meeting handouts, 2018 December 12; UA037.001510; 783.6 Kilobytes
    - Presentation on student conduct judicial process, 2018 December 12; UA037.001511; 57.9 Kilobytes
    - Additional undergraduates and housing issues, 2019 February 06; UA037.001512; 868.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2019 February 06; UA037.001513; 122.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 February 06; UA037.001514; 211.2 Kilobytes
    - Academic integrity policy review and recommendations, 2019 February 27; UA037.001515; 555.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2019 February 27; UA037.001516; 122 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 February 27; UA037.001517; 202 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee advising proposal, 2019 February 27; UA037.001518; 62.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2019 March 27; UA037.001519; 120.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 March 27; UA037.001520; 102.2 Kilobytes
    - Financial accessibility in the classroom presentation, 2019 March 27; UA037.001521; 754.7 Kilobytes
    - University financial presentation, 2019 March 27; UA037.001522; 1.2 MB Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 April 03; UA037.001523; 124.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda and briefing, 2019 April 24; UA037.001524; 120.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 April 24; UA037.001525; 153.5 Kilobytes
    - Athletics Committee concussion presentation, 2019 April 24; UA037.001526; 118.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2019 May 15; UA037.001527; 217 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 May 15; UA037.001528; 410.2 Kilobytes
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, Fall 2019; UA037.001529; 9.4 Megabytes; 17 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2019 August 27; UA037.001530; 30.2 Kilobytes
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 2019 August 27; UA037.001531; 250.9 Kilobytes
    - New faculty bios, 2019, 2019 August 27; UA037.001532; 131.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 September 11; UA037.001533; 237.8 Kilobytes
    - Plan for student divisions, 2019 September 11; UA037.001534; 1.5 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2019 October 16; UA037.001535; 191.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 October 16; UA037.001536; 211.9 Kilobytes
    - Mental Health Task Force Executive Summary, 2019 October 16; UA037.001537; 268.5 Kilobytes
    - Summer block schedule proposal, 2019 October 16; UA037.001538; 88.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2019 November 06; UA037.001539; 192.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 November 06; UA037.001540; 221.2 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee personal leave proposal, 2019 November 06; UA037.001541; 34.2 Kilobytes
    - University college presentation, 2019 November 06; UA037.001542; 868 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting agenda, 2019 December 04; UA037.001543; 221.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty meeting minutes, 2019 December 04; UA037.001544; 239.7 Kilobytes
    - Campus planning committee update, 2019 December 04; UA037.001545; 7.2 Megabytes
    - Letters of recommendation tips, 2019 December 04; UA037.001546; 75.1 Kilobytes
- Subject and Committee Files, 1858 -- 2015; 1945 -- 1999; UA037.002; 10.8 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) 1,648 files; 344 Megabytes
  This series consists of subject files related to the Secretary of the Faculty office that were received through the Office of the Dean of Arts and Sciences, as well as committee files received directly from the Secretary of the Faculty.
  This series is arranged alphabetically within accession.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - Subject Files, 1858 -- 2006; UA037.002.001
    - Academic Freedom / Tenure + Sabbatic Leave, 1918 -- 1982; UA037.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Activism, 1968 -- 1970; UA037.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee on Faculty Personnel, 1940 -- 1963; UA037.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Advisory Committee on Faculty Personnel: Sayre Case, 1963 -- 1966; UA037.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Arts and Sciences (1), 1915 -- 1982; UA037.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Arts and Sciences (2), 1960 -- 1988; UA037.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Crane School, 1959 -- 1965; UA037.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Engineering, 1968 -- 1985; UA037.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Fletcher School, 1956; UA037.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Graduate School, 1964 -- 1982; UA037.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - By Laws, Liberal Arts and Jackson, 1968 -- 1983; UA037.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Committees, 1972 -- 1982; UA037.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Educational T.V., 1954 -- 1965; UA037.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Faculty Reorganization, 1973; UA037.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Faculty Research Fund, 1958 -- 1975; UA037.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Library, 1915 -- 1981; UA037.002.001.00016 (Box 1)